David: I arrived at the Royal Albert Hall at seven o’clock.
I got the tickets, and I waited in the bar.
But Olivia didn’t arrive.
I looked at my watch. It was seven forty-five.
I looked at my phone. There was a message.
Olivia: Sorry! In a meeting.
Leave my ticket at the box office.
David: I left her ticket at the box office and went to my seat.
The concert started, but Olivia didn’t arrive.
When the concert finished, I phoned her,
but her phone was off.
W: The number you are dialling is currently unavailable.
David: I sent her a text:
Where are you?
I was very angry.
I left the concert hall and went home.
I opened the door of my flat and turned on the light…